Mr. Smith, you should've heard
what we just talked about.
En aquel entonces fue atropellado por un coche.
and I sold myself to pay for his surgery.
Después de eso, lo entendí mal y
signed that agreement with you out of anger.
Does that mean
you were forced to be with me?
¡Así es!
I really don't want to be with you. ¡Así es!
I really don't want to be with you.
Por eso no gasté ni un centavo
que diste durante estos cinco años.
Because I don't want to owe you.
Now that everything is resolved,
I want to return to him.
So, please Mr. Smith,
let me go, would you?
Of course, I'm grateful as well.
You've helped me a lot
when I was helpless.
But my feeling for you
is only binded by our agreement.
Eso es suficiente.
Álex,
Déjalos ir.
Clara.
Simón,
I need to tell you something.
Please ignore what I just said
in Henry's villa.
I said that because
I wanted to leave safely.
te espero
entender.
¿Por qué?
Forgive me, Simon.
I was the one who
betrayed you first.
You didn't betray me.
Sólo te vendiste a él
para salvarme.
Al principio fue así.
But later on,
I did it because I was willing to.
Are you in love with him?
si,
Estoy enamorada de él.
Gracias por llevarme a casa.
claire...